

SKILLS































LANGUAGES

SPANISH: Native

ENGLISH: Advanced (C2)

FRENCH: Basic
PORTUGUESE: Basic

CONTACT INFORMATION

Phone: +54 9 11 5147 6452

Address: Banfield, Buenos Aires (ARG) E-mail: ignacio.smirlian@hotmail.com Portfolio: <u>ignacio_smirlian_portfolio</u>

Linkedin: <u>ignacio-smirlian</u> Github: <u>Ignacio0104</u>

TX 5063

Ignacio Smirlian

Frontend Developer

ABOUT ME:

Hi! My name is Ignacio, and I'm starting my professional IT path.

I'm a passionate Frontend developer dedicated to creating interactive web experiences, skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React, among other technologies.

I like stepping out of my comfort zone in order to take up new challenges. I think of myself as a quick learner and a good team member. During all my different work experiences, I was able to prove to be a reliable, organized, and creative worker who is always willing to help their partners and go the extra mile to accomplish the team goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web UI Developer

GLOBANT | APRIL 2023 - PRESENT

- Develop and maintain visually appealing and user-friendly web pages using HTML, CSS, and React JS.
- Implement and maintain API integrations for data exchange between systems.
- Ensure that all components are responsive and accessible across different devices and platforms

Associate Professor

UTN | JULY 2022 - MARCH 2023

-Associate professor responsible for teaching Object-oriented programming, C# .NET on Visual Studio, Unit Testing, Multithreaded programming, Events and Delegates, and SQL.

Oracle Functional

GLOBANT | MARCH 2022 - APRIL 2023

- Analyze and provide solutions to JD Edwards users through an incident tickets system
- Understand the client's business and its processes
- Monthly analysis and reporting
- Suggest and work on system improvements whenever possible

Account Executive

GASTON-SACAZE DMC | MAY 2019 - MARCH 2022

- Preparation of tailor-made touristic packages.
- Group trip management
- Comprehensive tourist counseling on Argentina and Latin America.

Sales Executive

ATI VIAJES | APR 2018 - FEB 2019

- Assembly and quote of toursitic packages
- Trip counseling regarding activities, documentation, tours, etc.
- Billing and follow up service

EDUCATIONAL INFO

UTN - Facultad Regional de Avellaneda

TECHNICIAN IN PROGRAMMING | JUL 2021 - PRESENT

Unla - Universidad Nacional de Lanús

TOURISM BACHELOR'S DEGREE | 2013 - 2019

Sagrada Familia de Banfield

HIGH-SCHOOL BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN ECONOMICS AND ADMINISTRATION | 2009 - 2012